欢迎来到 Hugging Face 课程。
Welcome to the Hugging Face Course.
本课程旨在带您了解
This course has been designed to teach you
关于 Hugging Face 生态系统的一切
all about the Hugging Face ecosystem,
包括如何使用数据集和模型中心
how to use the dataset and model hub
以及我们所有的开源库。
as well as all our open-source libraries.
这是本课程的目录。
Here is the Table of Contents.
它共分为三个部分
As you can see, it's divided in three sections
由浅入深地带您学习。
which become progressively more advanced.
到目前为止，前两部分已经发布。
At this stage, the first two sections have been released.
在课程的一开始，我们会教您基础知识
So first, we'll teach you the basics
包括如何使用 Transformer 模型，
of how to use a Transformer model,
以及如何基于您自己的数据集上进行微调
fine-tune it on your own data set
并与社区分享结果。
and share the result with the community.
然后，我们将带您深入了解我们的开源库
So second, we'll dive deeper into our libraries
并教您如果能够处理任何 NLP 任务。
and teach you how to tackle any NLP task.
我们正在积极研究最后一部分
We're actively working on the last one
并希望在 2022 年春季完成并发布。
and hope to have it ready for you for the spring of 2022.
第一章不需要技术知识
The first chapter requires no technical knowledge
只会为您介绍一些基础知识
and is a good introduction to learn
例如 Transformers 模型可以做什么
what Transformers models can do
以及它如何帮助到您以及应用到您公司的业务中。
and how it could be of use to you or your company.
第一部分之后的章节需要具备 Python 的相关知识
The next chapters require a good knowledge of Python
以及机器学习和深度学习的
and some basic knowledge of
一些基础知识。
Machine Learning and Deep Learning.
如果您不知道什么是训练集和验证集
If you don't know what a training and validation set are
或者梯度下降法意味着什么，
or what gradient decent means,
您应该看看一些
you should look at an introductory course
诸如 deeplearning.ai 或 fast.ai 发布的入门课程
such as the ones published by deeplearning.ai or fast.ai.
如果您有一些关于某个
It's also best if you have some basics
深度学习框架、PyTorch 或 TensorFlow 中的基础知识那就更好了。
in one Deep Learning Framework, PyTorch or TensorFlow.
本课程介绍的各部分资料
Each part of the material introduced in this course
在 PyTorch 和 TensorFlow 中都有一个相对应的版本，
has a version in both those frameworks,
这样您就可以选择一个
so you will be able to pick the one
您最熟悉的版本。
you are most comfortable with.
这是开发这门课程的团队。
This is the team that developed this course.
接下来每位讲师会先
I'll now let each of the speakers
简单介绍一下自己。
introduce themselves briefly.
- Hi，我叫马修，
- Hi, my name is Matthew,
我是 Hugging Face 的机器学习工程师。
and I'm a Machine Learning Engineer at Hugging Face.
我在开源团队工作
I work on the open-source team
我负责维护
and I'm responsible for maintaining particularly
团队内的 TensorFlow 代码。
the TensorFlow code there.
在此之前，我是 Parsley 的机器学习工程师，
Previously, I was a Machine Learning Engineer at Parsley,
最近该公司被 Automatic 收购，
who've recently been acquired by Automatic,
我是一名博士后研究员
and I was a postdoctoral researcher
之前在爱尔兰都柏林三一学院
before that at Trinity College, Dublin in Ireland
致力于计算遗传学和视网膜疾病的研究。
working on computational genetics and retinal disease.
- Hi，我是 Lysandre
- Hi, I'm Lysandre.
我是 Hugging Face 的机器学习工程师
I'm a Machine Learning Engineer at Hugging Face
我是开源团队的一员。
and I'm specifically part of the open-source team.
我已经在 Hugging Face 团队和我的团队成员一起
I've been at Hugging Face for a few years now
工作了好几年，
and alongside my team members,
我一直致力于研究大多数您将在
I've been working on most of the tools
本课程中看到的工具。
that you'll get to see in this course.
- Hi，我是 Sylvain
- Hi, I'm Sylvain.
我是 Hugging Face 的研究工程师
I'm a Research Engineer at Hugging Face
也是 Transformers 代码库的主要维护者之一。
and one of the main maintainers of the Transformers Library.
之前，我在 fast.ai 工作
Previously, I worked at fast.ai
我帮助开发了 fast.ai 库
where I helped develop the fast.ai Library
以及在线图书。
as well as the online book.
在那之前，我是一名在法国的
Before that, I was a math and computer science teacher
数学和计算机科学老师。
in France.
- Hi，我叫 Sasha，是 Hugging Face 的一名研究员，
- Hi, my name is Sasha and I'm a Researcher at Hugging Face,
致力于道德，
working on the ethical,
机器学习模型的环境和社会影响相关的研究。
environmental and social impacts of machine learning models.
之前，我是 Mila 蒙特利尔大学的
Previously, I was a postdoctoral researcher at Mila,
博士后研究员
University in Montreal
我还为联合国全球脉搏计划担任过
and I also worked as an Applied AI Researcher
应用人工智能研究员。
for the United Nations Global Pulse.
参与过 CodeCarbon 和
I've been involved in projects such as CodeCarbon
机器学习影响计算器等项目
and the Machine Learning Impacts Calculator
致力于衡量机器学习的碳足迹的研究。
to measure the carbon footprint of machine learning.
- Hi，我是 Merve，我是 Hugging Face 团队的
- Hi, I'm Merve and I'm a Developer Advocate
开发技术推广工程师
at Hugging Face.
在此之前，我是一名机器学习工程师
Previously, I was working as a Machine Learning Engineer
负责构建 NLP 工具和聊天机器人。
building NLP tools and chat bots.
目前，我正在努力改进模型中心
Currently, I'm working to improve the hub
并使机器学习民主化。
and democratize machine learning.
- 大家好。
- Hello everyone.
我叫 Lucile，是 Hugging Face 团队的
My name is Lucile and I'm a Machine Learning Engineer
一名机器学习工程师
at Hugging Face.
用两句话告诉您我是谁，
To tell you in two sentences who I am,
我致力于开源工具的开发和支持
I work on the development and support of open-source tools
我也参与了在自然语言处理领域的
and I also participate in several research project
几个研究项目。
in the field of Natural Language Processing.
- 大家好。
- Good day there.
我是 Lewis，我是 Hugging Face 开源团队中的
I'm Lewis and I'm a Machine Learning Engineer
一名机器学习工程师。
in the open-source team at Hugging Face.
我热衷于为 NLP 社区开发工具
I'm passionate about developing tools for the NLP community
您可以在很多 Hugging Face
and you'll see me at many of Hugging Face's
对外的活动中见到我
outreach activities.
在加入 Hugging Face 之前，
Before joining Hugging Face,
我花了几年时间
I spent several years developing
为初创公司和 NLP 领域的企业
machine learning applications for startups
开发机器学习应用程序，
and enterprises in the domains of NLP,
以及拓扑数据分析和时间序列。
topological data analysis and time series.
在此之前，我是一名理论物理学家，
In a former life, I was a theoretical physicist,
负责在大型强子对撞机等
where I researched particle collisions
研究粒子碰撞。
at the Large Hadron Collider and so.
- Hey，我是 Leandro，我是一名 Hugging Face 开源团队中
- Hey, I'm Leandro and I'm a Machine Learning Engineer
的一名机器学习工程师
in the open-source team at Hugging Face.
在加入 Hugging Face 之前，我是一名在瑞士的数据科学家
Before joining Hugging Face, I worked as a Data Scientist
并在大学教授数据科学。
in Switzerland and have taught Data Science at University.